[
  { "question": "second (n)\n/ˈsek.ənd/", "answer": "giây" },
  { "question": "minute (n)\n/ˈmɪn.ɪt/", "answer": "phút" },
  { "question": "hour (n)\n/aʊr/", "answer": "giờ" },
  { "question": "day (n)\n/deɪ/", "answer": "ngày" },
  { "question": "week (n)\n/wiːk/", "answer": "tuần" },
  { "question": "month (n)\n/mʌnθ/", "answer": "tháng" },
  { "question": "year (n)\n/jɪr/", "answer": "năm" },
  { "question": "decade (n)\n/ˈdek.eɪd/", "answer": "thập kỷ" },
  { "question": "century (n)\n/ˈsen.tʃɚ.i/", "answer": "thế kỷ" },
  { "question": "millennium (n)\n/mɪˈlen.i.əm/", "answer": "thiên niên kỷ" },
  { "question": "morning (n)\n/ˈmɔːr.nɪŋ/", "answer": "buổi sáng" },
  { "question": "afternoon (n)\n/ˌæf.tɚˈnuːn/", "answer": "buổi chiều" },
  { "question": "evening (n)\n/ˈiːv.nɪŋ/", "answer": "buổi tối" },
  { "question": "night (n)\n/naɪt/", "answer": "ban đêm" },
  { "question": "midnight (n)\n/ˈmɪd.naɪt/", "answer": "nửa đêm" },
  { "question": "noon (n)\n/nuːn/", "answer": "buổi trưa" },
  { "question": "sunrise (n)\n/ˈsʌn.raɪz/", "answer": "bình minh" },
  { "question": "sunset (n)\n/ˈsʌn.set/", "answer": "hoàng hôn" },
  { "question": "today (n)\n/təˈdeɪ/", "answer": "hôm nay" },
  { "question": "yesterday (n)\n/ˈjes.tɚ.deɪ/", "answer": "hôm qua" },
  { "question": "tomorrow (n)\n/təˈmɔːr.oʊ/", "answer": "ngày mai" },
  { "question": "weekday (n)\n/ˈwiːk.deɪ/", "answer": "ngày trong tuần" },
  { "question": "weekend (n)\n/ˌwiːkˈend/", "answer": "cuối tuần" },
  { "question": "Monday (n)\n/ˈmʌn.deɪ/", "answer": "thứ Hai" },
  { "question": "Tuesday (n)\n/ˈtuːz.deɪ/", "answer": "thứ Ba" },
  { "question": "Wednesday (n)\n/ˈwenz.deɪ/", "answer": "thứ Tư" },
  { "question": "Thursday (n)\n/ˈθɝːz.deɪ/", "answer": "thứ Năm" },
  { "question": "Friday (n)\n/ˈfraɪ.deɪ/", "answer": "thứ Sáu" },
  { "question": "Saturday (n)\n/ˈsæt̬.ɚ.deɪ/", "answer": "thứ Bảy" },
  { "question": "Sunday (n)\n/ˈsʌn.deɪ/", "answer": "Chủ Nhật" },
  { "question": "January (n)\n/ˈdʒæn.ju.er.i/", "answer": "tháng Một" },
  { "question": "February (n)\n/ˈfeb.ruː.er.i/", "answer": "tháng Hai" },
  { "question": "March (n)\n/mɑːrtʃ/", "answer": "tháng Ba" },
  { "question": "April (n)\n/ˈeɪ.prəl/", "answer": "tháng Tư" },
  { "question": "May (n)\n/meɪ/", "answer": "tháng Năm" },
  { "question": "June (n)\n/dʒuːn/", "answer": "tháng Sáu" },
  { "question": "July (n)\n/dʒuːˈlaɪ/", "answer": "tháng Bảy" },
  { "question": "August (n)\n/ɑːˈɡʌst/", "answer": "tháng Tám" },
  { "question": "September (n)\n/sepˈtem.bɚ/", "answer": "tháng Chín" },
  { "question": "October (n)\n/ɑːkˈtoʊ.bɚ/", "answer": "tháng Mười" },
  { "question": "November (n)\n/noʊˈvem.bɚ/", "answer": "tháng Mười Một" },
  { "question": "December (n)\n/dɪˈsem.bɚ/", "answer": "tháng Mười Hai" }
]
